W. R. "Bob" Poage Campaign papers, Inclusive: 1898-1997, undated, Bulk: 1936-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Subject Files, 1918-1981, undated; 3
  - Newspapers, Announcements, Fees, and Requests, 1938-1940 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers, Announcements, Fees, and Requests, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, Clippings and Memos, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - O.H. Cross, Addresses and Clippings, 1922-1940 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - O.H. Cross, Legislative Record, 1936-1940 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - O.H. Cross, Remarks and Speeches, 1929-1940 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Other Politicians, Clippings, 1945-1948 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Organizations and Officials, Clippings, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Paul Quinn College, Coffee Reception, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Periodicals, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Perry Ellis, Clippings, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Poage Accomplishments, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Poage Memorials, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Political Announcements, Clippings and Correspondence, 1946 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Price Daniel, U.S. Senate Campaign, Clippings, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Printing Orders (1 of 2), 1940 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Printing Orders (2 of 2), 1940 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Ralph Nader, Questionnaire, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Retirement, Correspondence and Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Retirement, Draft of Speech, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Retirement Announcement, Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Richard C. Bush, Clippings and Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Richard C. Bush, Clippings, Promotional Materials, and Speeches, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Roster of Cameron Residents Who Attended Poage’s Campaign Speech, 1940 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Ruby Mae Travis, Clippings and Promotional Materials, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Statistics for District Development, Correspondence and Reports, 1972-1981 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Steve Alexander, Clippings, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Texas Elections and Constitution (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Texas Elections and Constitution (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Tom Connally, Clippings, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Voting Records, Seventy-First Congress, 1929-1931 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Voting Records, Seventy-Second Congress, 1931-1933 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Voting Records, Seventy-Third Congress, 1933-1934 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Voting Records, Seventy-Fourth Congress, 1935-1936 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Promotional Materials, 1898-1997, undated; 4
  Series IV. Promotional Materials consists of paper-based documents and three-dimensional objects relating to Congressman Bob Poage's election campaigns for the Texas and U.S. House of Representatives as well as other politicians' campaigns in the mid-twentieth century. Prominent materials include brochures, pins, stickers, and posters. The series is arranged alphabetically by material type and is in fairly good condition.
  - 1936 Campaign, 1935-1936 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Advertisements, circa 1936 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Advertisements, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Advertising Guides, 1953-1966, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Advertising Guides, 1972-1976, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Advertising Offers, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Advertising Offers and Samples, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Advertising Offers, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Announcements by County, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Blank Envelopes, “Bob Poage for Congress”, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Blank Envelopes and Stationary, “Bob Poage for Congress”, circa 1970 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Brochure, “He is Proven!”, circa 1972 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Brochure, “Jack Burgess is Prepared”, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Brochure, Lyndon B. Johnson, 1946 July 6 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Brochure, “Lyndon B. Johnson is the Man who is Doing the Job”, circa 1940’s (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Brochure, Marvin Leath for Congress, circa 1978 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Brochure, “State Senator W. R. (Bob) Poage Candidate for Congress”, circa 1936 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Brochures, “Poage is ProvenEL”, 1972-1976 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Brochures, “The Friends and Supporters of W. R. Poage Condemn Muck-Rakers and Mud Slinging”, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Brochures, “Who is the Farmer’s Friend in the Race of Congress?”, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Bumper Sticker, Leath for Congress, circa 1978 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Bumper Sticker, “Poage for Congress”, circa 1970 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Bumper Stickers, Jack Burgess for Congress, circa 1978 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Campaign Announcement Drafts, General and New Counties, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Campaign Cards, “Twelve Years Legislative Experience”, circa 1936 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Contribution Envelopes, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Card, “W. R. Poage for Representative Place No. 2”, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Card, “W. R. Poage for State Representative”, 1930 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Cards, 1944 Campaign (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Cards, Re-Election, circa 1940 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Frank Tirey Campaign, 1935-1936 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Index to Campaign Buttons, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Murray Watson, 1972 Campaign, 1972, undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - O.H. Cross, 1940 Campaign (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Photographic Materials, General Politicians, 1950-1965, undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Billboards, “Our Democratic Congressman Bob Poage”, circa 1970’s (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Picture Postcard Photographs and Negatives, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Pin, Bill Clinton Inauguration, 1997 January 20 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Pins, Adlai Stevenson for President, circa 1950’s (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Pins, American and Texan Flags, undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Pins, Ben Barnes for Governor of Texas, undated (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Pins, Binder, Scott Poage (1 of 4), 1898-1986, undated (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Pins, Binder, Scott Poage (2 of 4), 1898-1986, undated (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Pins, Binder, Scott Poage (3 of 4), 1898-1986, undated (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Pins, Binder, Scott Poage (4 of 4), 1898-1986, undated (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Pins, “Bob”, circa 1960’s (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Pins, Democratic Party, undated (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Pins, George McGovern for President, circa 1972 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Pins, Hubert Humphrey for President, circa 1968 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Pins, Jimmy Carter Re-Election, circa 1980 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Pins, John Connally for Governor of Texas, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Pins, John F. Kennedy for President, circa 1960 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Pins, Lyndon Johnson for President (1 of 2), circa 1964 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Pins, Lyndon Johnson for President (2 of 2), circa 1964 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Pins, “Poage is Proven”, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Pins, Preston Smith for Governor of Texas, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Pins, “Re-elect Poage for Congress”, circa 1950 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Pins, “Re-elect Poage to Congress”, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Pins, U.S. Congress (1 of 3), undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Pins, U.S. Congress (2 of 3), undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Pins, U.S. Congress (3 of 3), undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Poage Campaign Ads, Czech Community, 1972 (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Postcards, circa 1970 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Poster, “Keep Bob Poage in Congress!”, undated (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Poster, “Let’s Keep BobELHe’s Doing a Good Job”, 1972 (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Poster, “Poage is ProvenEL” (1 of 2), circa 1970 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Poster, “Poage is ProvenEL” (2 of 2), circa 1970 (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Poster, “Promote Poage — He is Qualified”, circa 1936 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Poster, “Re-elect W. R. Poage for Congress”, circa 1940 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Poster, “Re-elect W. R. Poage for Congress”, circa 1942 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Poster, “Re-elect W. R. Poage for Congress”, circa 1952 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Poster, “Who is the Friend of the Railroad Men?”, 1936 (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Posters, “Re-elect W. R. Poage for Congress”, circa 1960 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Posters, “State Senator W. R. Poage for Congress”, circa 1936 (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Posters, W. R. (Bob) Poage for Congress, circa 1936 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Radio Endorsements and Speeches, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Research Materials, Campaign Ideas, 1936-1938 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Sponsored Comics, 1952, undated (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Sticker, “Johnson/Humphrey for the USA”, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Stickers, “Best Wishes”, undated (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Stickers, Dolph Briscoe for Governor of Texas, undated (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Stickers, General Politicians, 1956-1957, undated (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Stickers, Vote Democratic, undated (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Wooden Nickel, W. Marvin Watson for Governor of Texas, undated (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Volunteer Cards, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 31)